Email | LinkedIn | GitHub

PROFILE

Professional with vast coordination and project management experience, in both media and IT driven work spaces. Recently graduated Web Development Bootcamp with Lighthouse Labs, a three-month intensive course teaching full-stack skills and technologies. Interested in joining a team in need of a fast-learning, fast-thinking Full-stack Junior Developer.

SKILLS

- Programming languages: JavaScript, SQL, HTML/CSS, Ruby
- Frameworks/libraries: NodeJS, Express, ReactJS, Axios, AJAX, jQuery, EJS, Material-UI, Bootstrap, SASS, ProgreSQL, Rails
- Testing: Mocha&Chai, Storybook, Jest, ESLint
- Complementary platforms: GitHub, GitHub Pages, Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, OneNote), Jira, Confluence, SharePoint, PowerApps, Axure, Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects)
- Agile methodologies, manual testing, bug management, coordination, management
- Team player, attention to detail, problem-solving, time management, pro-active
- Language skills: proficient English, intermediate French and Italian, native Romanian

PROJECTS

- <u>Echo replay your moments</u> a full-stack web app designed to allow its users to search for and save YouTube videos to their profile and save specific time snippets to that, which they can later play in a loop. (ReactJS, Express, PostgreSQL, SASS, Bootstrap)
- <u>uPick smart ToDo list</u> a full-stack app that works with external APIs to find information about movies, restaurants, books and products. It automatically adds the item to the correct list based on keywords. The user can later mark the item as done or edit to change name and category. (Express, PostgreSQL, EJS, SASS)
- <u>Scheduler</u> a single page application that allows students to book, edit or cancel interviews during weekdays. (**ReactJS**, **Express**, **PostgreSQL**, **StoryBook**, **Jest**, **Cypress**)
- <u>Tweeter</u> single-page Twitter clone that allows posting to a message board. (JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, HTML, CSS)
- <u>TinyApp</u> full-stack web app that allows users to shorten URLs (similar to bit.ly). (NodeJS, Express, EJS, Mocha&Chai)
- Jungle mini e-commerce application built with Rails 4.2.

Professional Training:

- Web Development Bootcamp, 2021 Montreal (Lighthouse Labs)
- Certified Tester Foundation Level, 2020, Montreal (ISTQB)
- SQL Basics for Data Science, 2020, Montreal (Coursera)
- Learn JavaScript, 2020, Montreal (Codecademy)
- Front End Fundamentals with JavaScript, 2019, Montreal (Lighthouse Labs)
- Certified trainer, 2009, Bucharest (Romanian National Council of Adult Professional Development)

Masters Degree, Audio-visual communications, 2013

National Academy for Political and Administrative Studies, Bucharest, Romania

Bachelor of Journalism, 2008

University of Bucharest, Faculty of Journalism, Bucharest, Romania

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Audit Sales Coordinator SweetIQ Analytics - Montreal, Canada

Apr 2017 - Jan 2020

- Reported bugs, liaised with sales and development team for platform inaccuracies or improvements (Jira)
- Managed audit reports for team and management use (Excel sheets, Microsoft PowerApps, PowerBI, HubSpot)

Online Sales Coordinator LULU Software - Montreal, Canada

Aug 2016 - Mar 2017

- Ensured timely delivery of projects by prioritizing and sprint planning bi-weekly managed projects calendar to follow up on progress (Excel+OneNote)
- Assisted sales team by coordinating day-to-day implementation of tasks creation, follow up, unblocking, mediate last minute additions or delays (Jira)

Website Editor

Jun 2015 - Jun 2016

Business Review Magazine - Bucharest, Romania

- Automated newsletter sending process, reducing its creation time by 60%
- Edited video materials for advertising campaign (Adobe After Effects, Illustrator)

Website Moderator & Support Telus International Europe - Bucharest, Romania

Oct 2014 - Jul 2015

• Moderated reported content on an international video hosting website and provided technical support in French and English

Media Coordinator / Office Assistant Bill&Melinda Gates Foundation - IREX - Bucharest, Romania

Mar 2009 - Feb 2014

- Managed online communication channels (website, blog, Facebook, Ushahidi crowdsourcing map and other support channels)
- Produced/edited multimedia materials (photo/video editing, graphics using Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects)